-没说明白  -不  说明白了
- It's not clear? - No, it's clear.
-我们说的是不行  -什么不行
- We're saying no. - No to what?
如果莉安娜接受了你的辞呈  我们也会辞职
If Leona accepts your resignations, we're resigning, too.
所有与热那亚事件有关系的人都会
Everyone who was involved with Genoa.
我不会接受你们的辞呈
I'm not going to accept your resignations.
恕我直言  若莉安娜接受了你的辞职
Due respect, but if Leona accepts yours,
就轮不到你...
you're not going to be in a position--
我们给你了一个坏报道  是我们的责任
We gave you a bad story. It's our responsibility.
这里是有原则的
There are principles of... principle here
有性格  有责任的
and character and responsibility.
你这都是从哪学来的
Who put all this in your head?
你啊  我们现在可以回去工作了吗
You did. Now can we go back to work?
你指望我哑口无言吗
You expect me to get choked up?
会议结束  两分钟归位
Meeting's over. Two minutes back.